Hey, you guys,
I got some bad news.
What?
Well, that's no way
to sell newspapers.
Try, "Extra, extra,
read all about it!"
No, Monica's restaurant got
a horrible review in the Post.
Oh, no!
Yeah, I didn't want
her to see it,
so I ran around
the neighborhood and bought
all the copies I could find.
Man, this is bad.
And I've had my share
of bad reviews.
I still remember
my first good one, though.
"Everything else in this
production of Our Town
"was simply terrible.
Joey Tribbiani was abysmal."
Hey... Oh, my God.
Look at all
the newspapers.
It must be a good review.
Is it great?
Um...
Oh, dear God.
But the good news is
no one in a two-block radius
will ever know.
What about the rest
of Manhattan?
Yeah, they all know.
Oh, my God,
this is horrible.
I'm so sorry, honey.
I'm so humiliated.
Yeah, but you know
what they say, Mon:
there is no such thing
as bad press.
You don't think
that, um
"The chef's mahi-mahi
was awful awful"
is bad press?
I didn't write it.
Oh, my God, is he right?
Am I really... am I awful?
ALL:
No.
Hey, Monica,
you listen to me, okay?
And I'm not just saying this
'cause I'm your friend.
I'm saying it
'cause it's the truth.
Your food is abysmal.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Ross?!
What? What?
I am freaking out.
Are you?
My due date is in one week.
What are you doing up?
That is seven days.
Okay, look, I had a lot of water
before I went to bed.
Can we do this after...?
No, no, no, no, no, Ross.
Please, come on--
we do not have any
of the big stuff that we need.
We do not have
a changing table.
a crib.
We do not have a diaper service.
It's funny you should
mention diapers.
I'm serious.
Okay, look, there's nothing
to worry about.
We have plenty of time.
There's a great
baby furniture store
on West Tenth.
Tomorrow we will
go there
and we'll get you
everything we need, okay?
Okay. Thank you.
That's great.
Thank you.
Wait, wait, where
on West Tenth?
'Cause there's a really
cute shoe store
that has, like...
Okay, okay, if, uh,
if you're going to do this
then I'm going
to go do that, so...
Oh, wait, Ross,
I'm sorry.
One more thing.
Yeah?!
Um, our situation, you know?
Um, what we mean to each other?
And, I mean
we're having this
baby together, you know
and we live together.
( sighing )
Isn't that... isn't that weird?
Well, uh...
I'm just kidding;
you can go pee.
Hey, uh, Monica,
I can't remember.
Did we say we were
going to meet here
or at the movie?
At the movies, but...
Okay, I'll see you there.
Joey...
now that you're here...
Sure, I can hang out
till I have to meet you.
But how come
you're not going?
I can't.
I've got a job interview
I got to get ready for.
I thought you already
have a job.
And people say
you don't pay attention.
No, no, this is
a much better job.
It's vice-president
of the company
that does data reconfiguration
and statistical factoring
for other companies.
Wow. How do you know
how to do that?
That's what I do now.
Hey, Joey,
come taste this.
What is it?
Remember that guy
that gave me a bad review?
Well...
I'm getting my revenge.
You cooked him?
No. He teaches a course
on food criticism
at the New School.
Before we go to the movies,
I'm going to go there
and make him try
my bouillabaisse again.
Oh, I can't wait
to read the front page
of the Post tomorrow.
"Restaurant reviewer
admits
'I was wrong
about Monica.'"
The front page?
MONICA:
Mm-hmm.
You really do live in your
own little world, don't you?
Do you, uh, want
these things delivered,
Mr. and Mrs. Geller?
Oh, no, no, no.
No, no, no,
we're not married.
We are having a baby together,
but we're not involved.
I mean, uh, we, we, we were
seeing each other a while ago
but then we were just friends
and then there
was one drunken night...
Or, "Yes, stranger, we'd like
this delivered, please."
Why don't you fill out
this address card?
Oh, okay.
I noticed you've
picked out a lot
of our dinosaur items.
RACHEL:
Oh, yeah.
Actually, that's one of the
reasons why we are not a couple.
I chose those.
I'm a paleontologist.
Really?
That is so cool.
Oh, oh, yeah, don't get
too worked up over it.
I mean, it sounds like
he's a doctor, but he's not.
Oh, no, no.
I'm fascinated
by paleontology.
Have you read the new
Walter Alvarez book?
I teach it in my class.
Oh, my God.
I'm standing
at a cash register
I'm holding a credit card,
and I'm bored.
Oh, I love
your neighborhood.
There's a great gym
right around the corner
from your building.
That's my gym.
I could tell you work out.
A paleontologist
who works out.
You're like Indiana Jones.
I am like Indiana Jones.
Hi, Pheebs.
Hey. Oh, how did
baby shopping go?
Oh, it was great.
We got everything
that we needed.
Oh, and Ross almost
got something
that wasn't on the list.
( clearing throat )
A whore.
What?
Well, we were paying
for our stuff
and this saleswoman just
started flirting with him.
Can you believe that?
Well, did she know
you two weren't married?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Well, the idea--
a woman flirting
with a single man--
we must alert
the church elders.
No, you don't understand.
You didn't see
how brazen she was.
It sounds like you're
a little jealous.
No, I'm not.
I-I-I just think it's wrong.
It, I mean, here I am
about to pop
and he's out picking up
some shop girl
at Sluts 'R Us?
Is that a real place?
Are they hiring?
Hey, Phoebe. Fatty.
Hey, Chandler,
why so fancy?
Well, I got
a job interview.
It's kind of
a big deal, too.
It's a lot more money
and I'd be doing
data reconfiguration
and statistical factoring.
Wait, I think I know
someone who does that.
Me. I do that.
So, seriously, do I,
do I look okay?
I'm a little nervous.
Oh, yeah, you really,
you look great.
Just don't get your hopes up.
Why not?
Well, the interview.
What about it?
You know. You don't make
a very good first impression.
What?
Oh, you don't know.
Are you serious?
Yes. When I first
met you
you were, like...
( speaking gibberish )
It was, like...
Shh!
What is it that I do?
Well, it's just like
you're trying too hard--
always making jokes, you know?
You come off a little needy.
Did you like me
when we first met?
Chandler, I'm not going to lie
to you.
But I am going to run away
from you.
Hi.
Um, I'm Monica Geller.
I'm the chef at Alesandro's.
Still?
I think the things
that you said
about me were really unfair
and I would like
for you
to give my bouillabaisse
another chance.
I don't see
any reason
why I would do that
to myself again.
Either eat it
or be in it.
Spoon?
( clearing throat )
So, what do you think?
I'm torn...
between my integrity
and my desire
to avoid a beating.
But I must
be honest.
Your soup...
is abysmal.
Attagirl!
Huh?!
We should get out of here.
There's a new class
coming in.
Welcome to "Introduction
to Cooking."
Now, before we start
can anyone tell me
the difference
between a hollandaise
and a béarnaise sauce?
I can.
Okay. Go ahead.
Well, they both have
an egg yolk
and butter base
but a béarnaise has
shallots, chervil
and, most importantly,
tarragon.
Oh, that's very good.
What's your name?
Monica.
Monica
you go to the head
of the class.
Okay.
Wow, all this stuff
takes up a lot of room.
Hey, how serious
are you
about keeping Ben
in your life?
My son?
Pretty serious.
( knock on door )
Well, hey, Katie.
What are you doing here?
Well, the delivery went out
to you
and I realized
they forgot this.
Must have been fairly obvious
since it was the only thing left
in your store.
Listen...
to be honest
home deliveries aren't
really part of my
job description.
Oh.
KATIE:
Oh, um...
I actually came here
to ask you out.
Oh, wow, uh...
yeah, sounds great.
Um, I'm just going
to put this
back in my pocket...
Pretend that
didn't happen.
Uh, yeah, actually,
I'm free now.
You want to grab
some coffee?
Sure.
Horny bitch.
No, you're a horny bitch.
No, you're
a horny bitch.
a horny bitch...
So you guys go.
Have a really
good time.
Okay, I'm just going
to grab my coat.
And, uh,
and my whip.
You know, because
of Indiana Jones.
( chuckling )
Not, not because
I'm into S&M.
I'm not
into anything weird.
Just, just normal sex.
So, I'm going
to grab my coat.
So, you had a good day, huh?
Big commission,
picked up a daddy.
Are you okay with this?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, please, you guys have fun.
Okay.
It was nice to see you.
Oh, and it was great
to see you, too.
And you look fantastic.
Although you missed a button.
Oh, uh, actually I, um...
Oh, okay,
I see what you're doing there.
I can't even
believe this.
I really come off
that badly?
Oh, it's okay.
You calm down after a while
and then people can see
how really sweet and wonderful
you really are.
Oh, good, good.
Because
I'm sure this interview
is going to last
a couple of weeks.
All right,
don't freak out, okay?
I, I will help you.
How long
before you have to leave?
An hour.
I can't help you.
Phoebe...
All right, all right
we'll just
do our best, okay?
So let's say that
I'm the interviewer
and I'm meeting you
for the first time.
Okay-- hi, come on in.
I'm Regina Fellangi.
Chandler Bing.
Oh, Bing.
What an unusual name.
Well, you should meet
my uncle, Bada.
I'll let myself out.
Hi.
Your fettuccine Alfredo
looks a little dry.
Did you use
all your cheese?
When you say "use"
do you mean eat
as a pre-cooking snack?
And the cream?
Cheese makes me thirsty.
Okay, let's move on.
All right.
Ooh, something smells good
over at Monica's station.
Oh, my God!
This is absolutely
amazing!
You've never
made this before?
Oh, no. I don't know
anything about cooking.
I had to ask someone
what it was called
when the water makes
those little bubbles.
Well, hats off to the chef.
I'm sorry, your mouth was full.
I didn't hear what you said.
Hats off to who, now?
The chef.
That's right.
I think you'll find
if I come to work here
that I don't micromanage.
I don't shy away from
delegating.
Mm-hmm, that's good to know.
But let's stop focusing on
what you don't do
and focus on what you do do.
What I do do...
is manage to create
an atmosphere of support
for the people working with me.
I see.
Nice sidestep on
the do do thing, by the way.
Hardest thing I've ever
done in my life.
You got to go!
Okay, don't worry.
You're ready.
Really?
Absolutely. Just fight all
your natural instincts
and you'll be great.
Ah, Monica,
my star student.
You know, you
called me that before
so I took the liberty of
fashioning a star
out of aluminum foil.
Now, no pressure.
You like my cookies,
you give me the star.
Mmm-mm-mm...
Wow, a star!
I know you all hate me
and I'm sorry,
but I don't care.
Okay, Joey,
you're up next.
Oh, my God!
This is amazing.
You get an A.
I got an A? In school?
Hey, I'm a dork!
Joey, I'm so proud of you.
I think you should
give him your star.
Excuse me?
He doesn't even know
what he's doing.
We're all beginners here.
Nobody knows
what they're doing.
I do. I'm a professional chef.
( all gasping )
Oh, relax. It's not
a courtroom drama.
If you're
a professional chef
what are you doing taking
Introduction to Cooking?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
It's just that, um...
I cook at this
restaurant, Alesandro's
and I just got
a really bad review.
Oh, Alesandro's!
I love that place.
You do?
Oh, yes.
You're an excellent chef.
As a person,
you're a little...
Oh, totally crazy,
but you like the food?
Very much.
Okay, then.
I don't stink.
I'm a good chef. Okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
I don't want to go.
I'm having fun.
Actually, did either of you
pay for this class?
Hey, hey, hey,
if my friend says
it's time to go,
it's time to go.
Also, I was the point person
on my company's transition
from the KL-5
to GR-6 systems.
You must have
had your hands full.
That I did. That I did.
So, let's talk a little bit
about your duties.
My doodies?
All right.
You'll be heading
a whole division
so you'll have a lot of duties.
I see.
But there'll be perhaps
30 people under you
so you can dump
a certain amount on them.
Good to know.
We could go into detail...
No, don't, I beg of you.
All right, then.
We'll have a definite answer
for you on Monday
but I think I can say
with some confidence
you'll fit in well here.
Really?
Absolutely.
You can relax.
You did great.
I got to say thank you.
I was really nervous.
I've been told
I come on too strong
make too many jokes
and then it was really hard
to sidestep that duty thing.
Duties.
( singsong ):
Poo.
Poo?
Oh, my God,
this doesn't count, okay?
The interview was over.
That was the real
Chandler Bing in there.
This is just some
crazy guy out in the hall.
Call security!
There's a crazy guy
out in the hall!
Poo?
I'll look forward
to your call.
Hi.
Hey, you're back from your date.
How are you?
I'm fine, but
that's not important.
What's important is how was she?
Uh, it was fun.
We just had coffee.
Oh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Coffee, a little rub-rub-rub
under the table.
What's going on?
Do you not like Katey?
No, no, she-she was nice.
I mean, she was a little slutty,
but who isn't?
I liked her.
Of course you did, Ross.
You would date a gorilla if
it called you Indiana Jones.
Did you get, like, a fresh batch
of pregnancy hormones today?
No, it's just that...
Katey bothered me.
Why? What was wrong with her?
There was nothing
wrong with her, all right?
She was perfectly
lovely.
Okay, so what's the matter?
I don't want you to date her.
Why? What, are you jealous?
Yes.
And not because I want you
to go out with me
because I don't want you
to go out with anybody.
Okay?
I know it's a terrible thing
to even think this
and it's completely
inappropriate
but I want you to be at
my constant beck and call
24 hours a day.
I'm very sorry
but that is just
the way that I feel.
Okay.
What?
I won't date.
I'll be here with you,
all the time.
Really?
But I'm being
so unreasonable.
True, but you're allowed
to be unreasonable.
You're having our baby.
Oh...
Ross, thank you, thank you.
You feel better?
No, not really.
You're pressing the baby
into my bladder
and now I have to pee.
Sorry.
Uh, Rach?
Yeah?
Just one thing.
We live together,
you're having our baby...
I'm not going to see
anybody else.
Are you sure you don't want
something more?
Wow.
I don't know. Maybe.
Rach, I was just messing around.
Like you did last night
when I had to pee.
I knew that, I knew that.
I was just
messing with you, too.
Okay, okay, because
for a minute you seemed...
No, no, no, no!
That's just 'cause
I'm such a good messer.
( laughs )
Rach?
Yeah?
The bathroom?
Right.
I had a great time.
Learned how to bake,
ate great food.
It's the first A I've gotten
since seventh grade
and I didn't have to sleep
with the teacher this time.
Oh, look,
acting for beginners.
Hey, want to feel good
about yourself?
What the hell.
Okay.
All right, let's start
with some basics.
Can anybody tell me
what the difference
between upstage
and downstage is?
Yeah, this was
a stupid idea.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org